Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(تَوأَم)
(Episode 15)
(الحلقة 15)
Do not come closer!
لا تقترب!
I will not...
لن أفعل...
I will not let you touch my savior!
لن اسمح لك بلمس منقذي!
Savior?
المخلص؟
I am going to kill you!
سوف أقتلك!
You wench!
يا فتاة!
How dare you kill your husband?
كيف تجرؤين على قتل زوجك؟
Xue Lian, fear not.
شيو ليان، لا تخافي.
If the good do not contend,
إذا لم يتنافس الصالحون،
they will only yield the way to the wicked.
فإنهم لن يفسحوا الطريق إلا للأشرار.
If you fear him,
إذا كنت تخاف منه،
you will be forced to kill yourself.
سوف تضطر إلى قتل نفسك.
If you are not afraid,
إذا لم تكن خائفا،
then he is nothing.
إذن فهو لا شيء.
Look.
ينظر.
Fighting back...
القتال مرة أخرى...
is not that hard.
ليس صعبا إلى هذه الدرجة.
You wench!
يا فتاة!
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Are you really going to kill me?
هل حقا ستقتلني؟
I will gut you!
سأقوم بتقطيعك!
You are right.
أنت محق.
I want to kill you!
أريد أن أقتلك!
For the past seven years,
على مدى السنوات السبع الماضية،
you forced me to go out every day to earn money for you.
لقد أجبرتني على الخروج كل يوم لكسب المال لك.
When things did not go well, you hit me and scolded me.
عندما لم تسير الأمور على ما يرام، ضربتني ووبختني.
And you even sold me off to be humiliated.
وحتى أنك بعتني لكي أهان.
An animal like you...
حيوان مثلك...
deserves to die!
يستحق الموت!
He is dead.
لقد مات.
I killed him myself.
لقد قتلته بنفسي.
My savior.
منقذي.
Thank you for bringing me back and freeing me.
شكرا لك على إرجاعي وتحريري.
I was able to get my revenge.
لقد تمكنت من الحصول على انتقامي.
That wench must have escaped home.
يبدو أن تلك الفتاة هربت من المنزل.
- Come on, search the place! - Search the place!
- هيا، ابحث عن المكان! - ابحث عن المكان!
They are here to silence me.
إنهم هنا لإسكاتي.
You should go. I do not want to drag you down.
يجب عليك أن تذهب. لا أريد أن أسحبك إلى الأسفل.
Stay here. I will deal with them.
ابقى هنا، سأتعامل معهم.
- My savior... - Stay put.
- منقذي... - ابقى في مكانك.
Come out!
يخرج!
Where is she? Speak!
أين هي؟ تكلم!
I do not know. Please spare me.
لا أعلم. أرجوك أنقذني.
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
Who gave you the guts...
من أعطاك الشجاعة؟
to set up a private brothel...
لإنشاء بيت دعارة خاص...
and disregard human lives?
والاستهتار بحياة البشر؟
Do you have a death wish?
هل لديك رغبة في الموت؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Who is your master?
من هو سيدك؟
He is no ordinary fighter.
إنه ليس مقاتلًا عاديًا.
He hid poison in his teeth. He is a suicide warrior.
لقد خبأ السم في أسنانه. إنه محارب انتحاري.
How did you end up provoking him?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر إلى استفزازه؟
When I was buying hairpins,
عندما كنت أشتري دبابيس الشعر،
I noticed that my seeds of longing had fallen off.
لقد لاحظت أن بذور شوقي قد سقطت.
Since you were buying sweet glutinous rice balls,
نظرًا لأنك كنت تشتري كرات الأرز الدبق الحلوة،
I went to look for it.
ذهبت للبحث عنه.
In the end, I bumped into a girl...
وفي النهاية، التقيت بفتاة...
who escaped from a secret brothel.
الذين هربوا من بيت دعارة سري.
And at the very end,
وفي النهاية،
it is as you see.
إنه كما ترى.
You are not mad, are you?
أنت لست مجنونا، أليس كذلك؟
Sorry to keep you waiting.
آسف لإبقائك في انتظار.
Next time you encounter something like this,
في المرة القادمة التي تواجه فيها شيئًا كهذا،
just tell me.
فقط أخبرني.
Eat it while it is hot.
تناوله وهو ساخن.
It will get cold soon.
سيصبح الجو باردًا قريبًا.
I will clear up these bodies.
سأقوم بتطهير هذه الجثث.
All right.
حسنًا.
After I was sold off,
بعد أن تم بيعي،
I was blindfolded by the human broker.
لقد تم تعصيب عيني من قبل الوسيط البشري.
They took me on a long carriage ride.
لقد أخذوني في رحلة طويلة بالعربة.
I even walked a long way through a secret passage.
حتى أنني مشيت مسافة طويلة عبر ممر سري.
When I got out of the secret passage,
عندما خرجت من الممر السري،
I found myself in an underground secret brothel.
وجدت نفسي في بيت دعارة سري تحت الأرض.
I could not bear such humiliation.
لم أستطع أن أتحمل مثل هذا الإذلال.
When the guards were not looking,
عندما لم يكن الحراس ينظرون،
I hid beneath the carriage where the bodies were hidden.
اختبأت تحت العربة حيث كانت الجثث مخفية.
That is how I escaped.
هكذا هربت.
Do you remember...
هل تذكر...
what was above the secret brothel?
ماذا كان فوق بيت الدعارة السري؟
I do not remember.
انا لا اتذكر.
I hid beneath the carriage.
لقد اختبأت تحت العربة.
I did not dare to speak,
لم أجرؤ على التكلم،
much less look around.
ناهيك عن النظر حولك.
However,
لكن،
I vaguely glimpsed through the cracks...
لقد نظرت من خلال الشقوق بشكل غامض...
and saw a few rows of big red lanterns.
ورأيت بضعة صفوف من الفوانيس الحمراء الكبيرة.
Big red lanterns?
الفوانيس الحمراء الكبيرة؟
Jifang House.
بيت جيفانج.
That is the Qiang people's favorite teahouse.
هذا هو بيت الشاي المفضل لشعب تشيانغ .
There is something off...
هناك شيء خاطئ...
about these Qiang people.
عن هؤلاء الناس تشيانغ.
I will send my men there now.
سأرسل رجالي إلى هناك الآن.
We will surround and wipe them out.
سوف نحاصرهم ونقضي عليهم.
No.
لا.
I heard from those inside...
سمعت من الموجودين بالداخل...
that the secret brothel was filled with explosives...
أن بيت الدعارة السري كان مليئا بالمتفجرات...
and full of traps.
ومليئة بالفخاخ.
If you force your way in,
إذا أجبرت نفسك على الدخول،
the mechanisms will trigger automatically,
سيتم تشغيل الآليات تلقائيًا،
and it will be blown to pieces at once.
وسوف يتم تفجيرها إلى قطع في الحال.
You are not thinking of sneaking in there...
أنت لا تفكر في التسلل إلى هناك...
and rescuing them yourself, are you?
وإنقاذهم بنفسك، أليس كذلك؟
My savior.
منقذي.
It is very dangerous in there.
إنه أمر خطير جدًا هناك.
I am familiar with the brothel.
أنا أعرف بيت الدعارة.
If anyone has to go, it should be me.
إذا كان على أي شخص أن يذهب، فيجب أن أكون أنا.
Master Xiao.
المعلم شياو.
What should we do then?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل إذن؟
I will go with you.
سأذهب معك.
Master, a girl escaped from the pavilion today.
سيدي، لقد هربت فتاة من الجناح اليوم.
I have sent men to pursue and kill her.
لقد أرسلت رجالاً لمطاردتها وقتلها.
So useless!
عديمة الفائدة!
If this happens again,
إذا حدث هذا مرة أخرى،
you will have to pay for it with your life.
سوف تضطر إلى دفع ثمن ذلك بحياتك.
Yes.
نعم.
Arrange for a new batch of girls.
ترتيب لمجموعة جديدة من الفتيات.
Make sure our guests have a good time.
تأكد من أن ضيوفنا يقضون وقتًا ممتعًا.
Yes.
نعم.
Chief.
رئيس.
We found the human broker.
لقد وجدنا الوسيط البشري.
The black market sent word...
السوق السوداء أرسلت كلمة...
that they are sending in new girls tonight.
أنهم يرسلون فتيات جديدات الليلة.
Prepare some rouge and embroidery work.
تحضير بعض أعمال الروج والتطريز.
Move!
يتحرك!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Get moving!
تحرك!
Faster!
أسرع!
Move!
يتحرك!
There are beauties.
هناك جميلات.
I have a lot of money.
لدي الكثير من المال.
I want to buy all of them.
أريد أن أشتريهم جميعا.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Do not get yourself killed.
لا تتسبب في قتل نفسك.
If you know what is good for you, scram!
إذا كنت تعرف ما هو جيد بالنسبة لك، فانصرف!
Sir, I failed to recognize your standing.
سيدي، لقد فشلت في التعرف على مكانتك.
I will leave now. At once.
سأغادر الآن. فورًا.
The carriage is coming.
العربة قادمة.
Check their blindfolds again.
تحقق من العصابات التي تغطي أعينهم مرة أخرى.
One, two, three, four, five,
واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة، أربعة، خمسة،
- Wear your blindfolds properly! - six, seven,
- ارتدِ عصابة العينين بشكل صحيح! - ستة، سبعة،
- Behave! - eight, nine, ten, eleven,
- تصرف! - ثمانية، تسعة، عشرة، أحد عشر،
twelve.
اثنا عشر.
I remember I caught 10 girls.
أتذكر أنني أمسكت بعشر فتيات.
Why is it 12 now?
لماذا أصبح 12 الآن؟
Two more people mean two more payments.
شخصان آخران يعنيان دفعتين إضافيتين.
Move out!
إخرج!
Keep up and move faster!
واصل التقدم وتحرك بشكل أسرع!
Go.
يذهب.
Move, hurry up.
تحرك، اسرع.
Hurry up. I'm talking to you.
أسرع، أنا أتحدث إليك.
- Behave! - Move your feet.
-تصرف! - حرك قدميك.
Get moving!
تحرك!
Why is this path so familiar?
لماذا هذا المسار مألوف جدًا؟
- Go! - Come on.
- اذهب! - هيا.
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
And this smell...
وهذه الرائحة...
Could this place be...
هل يمكن أن يكون هذا المكان...
Zhaoyue Pavilion?
جناح تشاويو؟
- Stay close! - Faster.
- ابقى قريبًا! - أسرع.
Later, when our honored guest comes,
وفي وقت لاحق، عندما يأتي ضيفنا الكريم،
you must treat him well.
يجب عليك أن تعامله بشكل جيد.
If our honored guest is even the slightest dissatisfied,
إذا كان ضيفنا الكريم غير راضٍ ولو قليلاً،
I will tear your face off.
سأمزق وجهك.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
My little beauty.
جمالي الصغير.
Stop hiding.
توقف عن الاختباء.
Come out and play with me.
تعال والعب معي.
Come on out,
تعالوا للخارج
little beauty.
القليل من الجمال.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
If I catch you,
إذا أمسكتك،
I will punish you, yes?
سأعاقبك، أليس كذلك؟
- This way. - My little beauty.
- من هنا. - جميلتي الصغيرة.
My little beauty, where are you?
جميلتي الصغيرة، أين أنت؟
Are you playing hide-and-seek with me?
هل تلعب معي لعبة الغميضة؟
Do not let me catch you later.
لا تدعني أمسكك لاحقًا.
Hush.
صمت.
Do not laugh. If you do, I will kiss you.
لا تضحك، إذا فعلت، سأقبلك.
So this is the Qiang leader hiding in Ying.
إذن هذا هو زعيم تشيانغ المختبئ في ينغ.
He must be today's honored guest.
لا بد أنه الضيف الكريم اليوم.
You cannot kill him here.
لا يمكنك قتله هنا.
- My little beauty. - Otherwise,
- جميلتي الصغيرة. - وإلا،
we cannot interrogate him.
لا يمكننا استجوابه.
- You are still laughing? - Where are you?
- مازلت تضحك؟ - أين أنت؟
I will stall him here.
سأوقفه هنا.
You go find the gunpowder.
اذهب للبحث عن البارود.
You?
أنت؟
- What? Can't I? - My little beauty.
- ماذا؟ ألا أستطيع؟ - يا جميلتي الصغيرة.
- Okay. - If I find you,
-حسنا. - إذا وجدتك،
there will be a punishment.
سيكون هناك عقاب.
I am going.
وانا ذاهب.
Come out, my little beauty.
إخرجي يا جميلتي الصغيرة.
Honored guest.
ضيف شرف.
Are you looking for me?
هل تبحث عني؟
So tasty!
لذيذ جداً!
They really picked a tasty one for me this time.
لقد اختاروا لي حقا شيئا لذيذا هذه المرة.
- Beauty. - Hush.
- جمال. - هش.
Do not be nice to me.
لا تكن لطيفا معي.
Honored guest,
ضيف شرف،
slow down.
ابطئ.
All right.
حسنًا.
Come here, my little beauty.
تعالي هنا يا جميلتي الصغيرة.
- Very well. - Good wine goes well with beauties.
- حسنًا جدًا. - النبيذ الجيد يتناسب جيدًا مع الجمال.
Do not run!
لا تركض!
Hey, pretty lady.
مرحبا سيدتي الجميلة.
We all call the madam of the secret brothel...
نحن جميعا نطلق على سيدة بيت الدعارة السري...
"Mother."
"الأم."
If any of the new girls refused to take clients,
إذا رفضت أي من الفتيات الجدد قبول العملاء،
she would hand them over to her men...
ستسلمهم لرجالها...
to be abused and killed.
أن يتم إساءة معاملته وقتله.
She likes to drink when she checks the books.
إنها تحب الشرب عندما تتحقق من الكتب.
She also has a special enamel wine set.
كما أنها تمتلك مجموعة خاصة من النبيذ المينا.
There are guards stationed on her floor.
هناك حراس متمركزين في طابقها.
Why are you so slow?
لماذا انت بطيئا جدا؟
- Mother is getting impatient. - Forgive me, I am useless.
- أمي أصبحت غير صبورة. - سامحني، أنا عديم الفائدة.
Mother asked me to bring her a jar of wine.
طلبت مني أمي أن أحضر لها جرة من النبيذ.
- Go upstairs. - Yes.
- اصعد إلى الطابق العلوي. - نعم.
Mother.
الأم.
I have brought you some wine.
لقد أحضرت لك بعض النبيذ.
Come in.
ادخل.
Mother.
الأم.
Where did you hide the gunpowder?
أين أخفيت البارود؟
Who sent you?
من أرسلك؟
You do not deserve to know.
أنت لا تستحق أن تعرف.
Then no one will be there to bury you!
حينها لن يكون هناك أحد ليدفنك!
If you dare make a sound,
إذا تجرأت على إصدار صوت،
I will pierce your throat.
سأثقب حنجرتك.
Can you tell me now...
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني الآن...
where the gunpowder is hidden?
أين يتم إخفاء البارود؟
I will tell you.
سأخبرك.
The gunpowder is hidden behind this wall.
البارود مخفي خلف هذا الجدار.
That candlestick is the trigger.
هذه الشمعة هي المحفز.
The gunpowder is hidden in the room.
تم إخفاء البارود في الغرفة.
Are you not afraid of blowing yourself up if it goes off?
ألا تخاف من تفجير نفسك إذا انفجرت؟
My master hired a specialist to design the secret room.
لقد استأجر سيدي متخصصًا لتصميم الغرفة السرية.
As long as it is not forced,
طالما أنه ليس قسرا،
it will not go off accidentally.
لن تنفجر عن طريق الخطأ.
How do we destroy the mechanism controlling the gunpowder?
كيف ندمر آلية التحكم بالبارود؟
The candlestick's wick is the fuse for the explosives.
فتيل الشمعة هو الفتيل للمتفجرات.
All you have to do...
كل ما عليك فعله...
is pull it out.
هو سحبه للخارج.
Who is your master?
من هو سيدك؟
I... I really do not know.
أنا... أنا حقا لا أعرف.
He always wears a mask when he comes.
هو يرتدي قناعًا دائمًا عندما يأتي.
I have never seen his real face.
لم أرى وجهه الحقيقي أبدًا.
You do not know?
أنت لا تعرف؟
Then you are useless.
إذاً أنت عديم الفائدة.
I was right.
لقد كنت على حق.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
No way.
مستحيل.